<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>rirespira on Giulio Starace</title>
    <link>http://www.giuliostarace.com/tags/rirespira/</link>
    <description>Recent content in rirespira on Giulio Starace</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.giuliostarace.com/tags/rirespira/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rirespira DevBlog 3 | Re-think</title>
      <link>http://www.giuliostarace.com/posts/rirespira-3-re-think/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.giuliostarace.com/posts/rirespira-3-re-think/</guid>
      <description>So, it&amp;rsquo;s been a while. It&amp;rsquo;s been more than a month, in fact, since the last time I committed anything to my Rirespira git repository, which includes planning documents.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been quite busy to say the least; since my last commit I have moved to a new continent and started a 6-month internship which will keep me busy here until the beginning of February.
Moving to a new continent, on my own, where the language spoken is neither Italian nor English, has definitely taken up quite a bit of my time and energy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rirespira DevBlog 2 | The Tech Stack</title>
      <link>http://www.giuliostarace.com/posts/rirespira-2-tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.giuliostarace.com/posts/rirespira-2-tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>So I have somewhat introduced the concept behind Rirespira, but how will it be implemented from a technological point of view?
Rirespira will be a website. With the mobile app market dying down, frameworks becoming more and more suitable for mobile web development and internet connectivity becoming increasingly accessible, for me it only makes sense for most projects be web-based.
The nature of a browser-based Rirespira will require a front-end, a back-end and a database before being deployed, like most dynamic websites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rirespira DevBlog 1 | The Concept</title>
      <link>http://www.giuliostarace.com/posts/rirespira-1-concept/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.giuliostarace.com/posts/rirespira-1-concept/</guid>
      <description>For the last three years I have been living in the UK, particularly up north in Durham where the climate throughout the year doesn&amp;rsquo;t really lend itself to a strong agricultural economy when it comes to vegetables other than potatoes and carrots.
The result is the presence of a huge proportion of imported vegetables in supermarkets, often from across the Atlantic and often packaged in plastic to prolong their shelf life.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>