<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Giulio Starace</title>
    <link>https://www.giuliostarace.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Giulio Starace</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 23:19:16 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.giuliostarace.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rirespira DevBlog 2 | The Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://www.giuliostarace.com/blog/rirespira-devblog-2--the-tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 23:36:15 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.giuliostarace.com/blog/rirespira-devblog-2--the-tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>So I have somewhat introduced the concept behind Rirespira, but how will it be implemented from a technological point of view?
Rirespira will be a website. With the mobile app market dying down, frameworks becoming more and more suitable for mobile web development and internet connectivity becoming increasingly accessible, for me it only makes sense for most projects be web-based.
The nature of a browser-based Rirespira will require a front-end, a back-end and a database before being deployed, like most dynamic websites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rirespira DevBlog 1 | The Concept</title>
      <link>https://www.giuliostarace.com/blog/rirespira-devblog-1--the-concept/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 17:32:39 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.giuliostarace.com/blog/rirespira-devblog-1--the-concept/</guid>
      <description>For the last three years I have been living in the UK, particularly up north in Durham where the climate throughout the year doesn&amp;rsquo;t really lend itself to a strong agricultural economy when it comes to vegetables other than potatoes and carrots.
The result is the presence of a huge proportion of imported vegetables in supermarkets, often from across the Atlantic and often packaged in plastic to prolong their shelf life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why blog?</title>
      <link>https://www.giuliostarace.com/blog/why-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 16:41:28 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.giuliostarace.com/blog/why-blog/</guid>
      <description>There is a &amp;ldquo;syndrome&amp;rdquo; I suffer from that could easily be called &amp;ldquo;nebulous thoughts syndrome&amp;rdquo;. In a way, you could describe it as daydreaming. While cooking, showering, walking to classes, walking in general or while doing whatever other random activity, I very often catch my mind drifting, thinking about all sorts of different matters.
I&amp;rsquo;m sure we all get caught up in this but for me it ends up being relatively frustrating - I find that because of the hazy nature of these inner discussions, they often do not find any solid conclusions, simply morphing into new topics, often overly emotionally influenced and opinionated, lacking any form of fact-checking and structure.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>